<?xml version="1.0"?>
<cookbook><recipe id="r689c4fc5546a2"><title>Chocolate Mug Cake</title><ingredients>all-purpose flour, sugar, cocoa powder, baking powder, milk, vegetable oil, vanilla extract, salt</ingredients><steps>1. In a microwave-safe mug, add 4 tablespoons of all-purpose flour, 4 tablespoons of sugar, and 2 tablespoons of cocoa powder.&#xD;
&#xD;
2. Add 1/8 teaspoon of baking powder and a pinch of salt. Mix well.&#xD;
&#xD;
3. Pour in 3 tablespoons of milk, 2 tablespoons of vegetable oil, and 1/4 teaspoon of vanilla extract. Stir until smooth.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. Microwave on high for 1 minute to 1 minute 30 seconds, until the cake has risen and is set in the middle.&#xD;
&#xD;
5. Let it cool for a minute, then enjoy straight from the mug.</steps><tags>dessert, quick, chocolate, easy</tags></recipe><recipe id="r689c500c66425"><title>Garlic Butter Pasta</title><ingredients>spaghetti, butter, garlic, olive oil, salt, black pepper, parsley, parmesan cheese</ingredients><steps>1. Cook spaghetti according to package instructions in salted boiling water until al dente. Reserve 1/2 cup pasta water, then drain.&#xD;
&#xD;
2. In a large pan, melt 2 tablespoons butter with 1 tablespoon olive oil over medium heat.&#xD;
&#xD;
3. Add 3 minced garlic cloves and saut&#xE9; for 1&#x2013;2 minutes until fragrant.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. Add the drained pasta to the pan and toss to coat in the garlic butter mixture.&#xD;
&#xD;
5. Add a splash of reserved pasta water if needed to loosen the sauce.&#xD;
&#xD;
6. Season with salt and black pepper to taste.&#xD;
&#xD;
7. Garnish with chopped parsley and grated parmesan cheese before serving.</steps><tags>pasta, quick, dinner, vegetarian</tags></recipe><recipe id="r689c50ac7933e"><title>Vegetable Fried Rice</title><ingredients>cooked rice, carrot, capsicum, green peas, onion, garlic, soy sauce, vinegar, salt, black pepper, spring onions, oil</ingredients><steps>1. Heat 2 tablespoons oil in a large pan or wok over medium-high heat.&#xD;
&#xD;
2. Add 2 cloves minced garlic and 1 diced onion, and saut&#xE9; until translucent.&#xD;
&#xD;
3. Add diced carrot, capsicum, and green peas; stir-fry for 3&#x2013;4 minutes until tender but crisp.&#xD;
&#xD;
4. Push the vegetables to the side and add the cooked rice.&#xD;
&#xD;
5. Pour in 2 tablespoons soy sauce and 1 teaspoon vinegar; mix well.&#xD;
&#xD;
6. Season with salt and black pepper to taste.&#xD;
&#xD;
7. Garnish with chopped spring onions before serving.</steps><tags>rice, vegetarian, quick, asian</tags></recipe></cookbook>
